

Hoiman Christy Chan

UI/UX Designer in San Francisco



www.behance.net/christykchan



christychan04@gmail.com



(510) 598 - 6600



Oakland, CA

PROFILE

UI/UX designer experienced in solving problems and providing solutions with different clients daily. Enthusiastic in curating user-centric solutions and transforming ideas into appealing designs. Great at teamwork, fast learning, and optimizing work processes to enhance user experiences.

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX DESIGNER - INDUSTRIAL PROJECT (NDA) 01/2020 - 05/2020 Springboard

- Worked with the head of the start-up company to perform usability tests with 5
 participants on the existing prototype, improved and redesigned user flow, user
 interface, and the overall product in a total of 24 screens.
- Collaborated with two stakeholders and one design lead daily to achieve the project goal. Adapted with deadlines, timeframes, and different work styles in the team.

PERSONAL BANKER

12/2017 - 08/2020

Wells Fargo Bank - Oakland, CA

- Listened to clients' problems and needs to provide different solutions to solve their problems and help them succeed financially.
- Assisted branch manager to coach other team members on improving customer interactions and educating them with our products and services.

BANK TELLER

06/2016 - 12/2017

Wells Fargo Bank - Oakland, CA

 Assisted service manager with the branch's daily tasks such as vault balancing and other safety measures and ensured they were completed promptly.

UI/UX SKILLS

- DESIGN THINKING
- CREATIVE SOLUTION
- USER INTERVIEW
- OSEK INTERVIEW
- AFFINITY MAP
- PERSONAEMPATHY MAP

- USER JOURNEY MAP
- USABILITY HEURISTIC
- USER FLOW
- USER INTERFACE DESIGN
- LOW-HIGH FIDELITY PROTOTYPE
- USABILITY TEST
- FEEDBACK LOOP

SOFTWARE



M ADOBE XD

in INVISION

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

HTML Beginner

CSS
Beginner

JAVASCRIPT
Beginner

EDUCATION

UI DESIGN CERTIFICATION

07/2021 - 03/2022 Career Foundry

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT FOR DESIGNERS

01/2022 - 03/2022 Career Foundry

UX DESIGN CERTIFICATION

08/2019 - 09/2020 Springboard

COMMUNICATION GRAPHICS

09/2012 - 06/2014 Laney College

GRAPHIC DESIGN MAJOR

09/2011 - 06/2012 Pasadena City College

LANGUAGES



CHINESE

- Cantonese
- Mandarin

